Finding Aid for the Verley Archer Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Box Listing
  - Series II: Vanderbilt University Centennial
    - Responses to William H. Vanderbilt, re: Reunion (5 of 5) (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Associates Program Mailing List (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Associates Program Roster (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Mailing Lists of Vanderbilt Descendants (1 of 4) (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Mailing Lists of Vanderbilt Descendants (2 of 4) (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Mailing Lists of Vanderbilt Descendants (3 of 4) (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Mailing Lists of Vanderbilt Descendants (4 of 4) (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - List of Descendants Attending the Centennial (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Gifts from Vanderbilt Descendants to, July, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Samples of Mailings to Vanderbilt Descendants (1 of 3) (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Samples of Mailings to Vanderbilt Descendants (2 of 3) (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Samples of Mailings to Vanderbilt Descendants (3 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Vanderbilt Centennial Planning Materials (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Vanderbilt Descendants Book---Drafts and Charts (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Vanderbilt Descendants Book---Draft Copy (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Vanderbilt Descendants Book---Master Copy and Index (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Vanderbilt Descendants Book, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Vanderbilt Descendants Book---Publication Information (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Vanderbilt Centennial---Local Arrangements for Vanderbilt Descendants (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Vanderbilt University---Centennial of Founding, March 16-17, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Vanderbilt University---Centennial of Opening, October 3, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Two metal file boxes---Current (1972) Addresses for Vanderbilt Descendants (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Series III: Research Materials
    - Verley Archer Research Materials---General Research Materials (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Verley Archer Research Materials---Memos, Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Vanderbilt Family Obituaries, Engagement, and Marriage Announcements (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Articles about Vanderbilt Family Members (1 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Articles about Vanderbilt Family Members (2 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Articles about Vanderbilt Family Members (3 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Vanderbilt Family Houses and Mausoleum (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Verley Archer’s Research, 1977-80 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Verley Archer’s General Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Verley Archer’s Research---General (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Verley Archer’s Research---Vanderbilt Family (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Research Notes, Aug. 28-31, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Additional Research Notes (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Materials for Quotation (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Research---Mrs. William Astor (Caroline Schermerhorn) (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Research---Pulitzer by W.A. Swanberg (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Publications by Descendants of the Commodore or Their Spouses (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Publications About or Including Vanderbilts (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Foundations with Which Descendants of the Commodore Are Associated (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - William K. Vanderbilt Museum, Centerport, Long Island, New York (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Vanderbilts Distantly Related But Not Descendants of the Commodore (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Vanderbilt Descendants Book---updated, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Vanderbilt Descendants Book---updated, 1982 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - History of Vanderbilt University by Edwin Mims (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Higinbotham: An Encyclopedic Genealogy, Vols. One and Two by Norman L. Higinbotham, (1970) (Box 20, Folder 3)